According to a recent study, a small but growing proportion of the workforce is affected to some degree by a sense of entitlement.
根据最近的一项研究，劳动者中有一小部分人在某种程度上受到特权心态的影响，而且这部分人所占的比例还在不断上升。
Work is less about what they can contribute and more about what they can take.
对他们而言，工作与其说关乎自己能贡献什么，不如说关乎自己能索取什么。
It can lead to workplace dysfunction and diminish their own job satisfaction.
这种心态可能导致职场运转失常，并降低他们自身的工作满意度。
I’m not referring to employees who are legitimately dissatisfied with their employment conditions due to, say, being denied fair pay or flexible work practices.
我指的不是那些有正当理由对雇佣条件感到不满的员工，比如说，因为得不到公平的薪酬或无法采用灵活的工作方式而不满的人。
I’m talking about those who consistently believe they deserve special treatment and generous rewards.
我说的是那些始终认为自己理应得到特殊待遇和丰厚回报的人。
It’s an expectation that exists irrespective of their abilities or levels of performance.
无论他们的能力或业绩水平如何，这种期望都存在。
As a result of that discrepancy between the privileges they feel they’re owed and their actual performance, and of their inflated sense of self-worth, they don’t work as hard for their employer.
由于自认为应得的特权与实际业绩之间存在这种落差，再加上自我价值感过高，他们为雇主工作就没那么卖力。
They prefer instead to slack off.
相反，他们宁愿偷懒懈怠。
It’s a tendency which many scholars believe begins in childhood due to parents who overindulge their kids.
许多学者认为，这种倾向始于童年，原因是父母过度溺爱孩子。
This leads them to expect the same kind of spoilt treatment throughout their adult lives.
这导致他们成年以后也一直期望得到同样的娇惯待遇。
And yet despite how these employees feel, it’s obviously important for their manager to nonetheless find out how to keep them motivated.
然而，尽管这些员工抱有这样的心态，对他们的经理来说，弄清楚如何让他们保持积极性显然仍然很重要。
And, by virtue of that heightened motivation, performing well.
并且让他们凭借由此提高的积极性，保持良好的表现。
The research team from several American universities surveyed more than 240 individuals.
来自美国几所大学的研究团队调查了240多人。
They sampled managers as well as team members.
他们抽样调查的对象既有经理，也有团队成员。
Employee entitlement was measured by statements such as “I honestly feel I’m just more deserving than others.”
员工特权心态用诸如“说实话，我觉得自己就是比别人更有资格”这样的陈述来衡量。
The respondents had to rate the extent of their agreement.
受访者需要评定自己在多大程度上同意这些说法。
Employee engagement, meanwhile, was assessed with statements like “I really throw myself into my work.”
而员工敬业度则用“我真的全身心投入工作”之类的陈述来评估。
The findings revealed ethical leadership is precisely what alleviates the negative effects of employee entitlement.
研究结果表明，缓解员工特权心态负面影响的，恰恰是道德型领导。
That’s because rather than indulging employees or neglecting them, ethical leaders communicate very direct and clear expectations.
这是因为道德型领导者既不纵容员工，也不忽视员工，而是传达非常直接、明确的期望。
They also hold employees accountable for their behaviors and are genuinely committed to doing the right thing.
他们还要求员工为自己的行为负责，并真心致力于做正确的事。
Additionally, these leaders are consistent in their standards.
此外，这些领导者的标准始终如一。
They’re also less likely to deviate in how they treat employees.
在对待员工的方式上，他们出现偏差的可能性也更小。
This means, when confronted by an entitled team member, an ethical leader is significantly disinclined to accommodate their demands.
这意味着，道德型领导者在面对有特权心态的团队成员时，会明显不愿迁就对方的要求。
He or she will instead point out, constructively and tactfully, exactly how their inflated sense of deservingness is somewhat distorted.
相反，领导者会以建设性而又得体的方式，确切地指出对方过高的应得感在哪些方面有些扭曲。
He or she will then go further to explain the specific, and objective, criteria the employee must meet to receive their desired rewards.
接着，领导者还会进一步说明，这名员工必须达到哪些具体而客观的标准，才能获得自己想要的回报。
This shift away from unrealistic expectations is successful because entitled employees feel more confident that ethical leaders will deliver on their promises.
这种摆脱不切实际期望的转变之所以成功，是因为有特权心态的员工更加确信，道德型领导者会兑现承诺。
This occurs because they’re perceived to be fair and trustworthy.
之所以会这样，是因为这些领导者被视为公平、值得信赖的人。
The researchers, however, exercise caution by warning that no one single response is the perfect remedy.
然而，研究人员保持谨慎，提醒说没有哪一种单一的应对措施是完美的解决办法。
But there’s no denying ethical leadership is at least a critical step in the right direction.
但不可否认的是，道德型领导至少是朝正确方向迈出的关键一步。